<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Tokens version="1.0">
	<File path="Constants/DJIVirtualStickRollPitchControlMode.html">
		
		<Token>
			<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/c/tdef/DJIVirtualStickRollPitchControlMode</TokenIdentifier>
			<Abstract type="html">Defines how manual roll and pitch values are interpreted by the aircraft.</Abstract>
			<DeclaredIn>DJIFlightController.h</DeclaredIn>
            
			
			<NodeRef refid="157"/>
		</Token>
		
		
        
        <Token>
            <TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/c/econst/DJIVirtualStickRollPitchControlModeAngle</TokenIdentifier>
            <Abstract type="html">Sets the VirtualStickControlMode roll and pitch values to be an angle relative to
a level aircraft. In the body coordinate system, positive and negative pitch angle is for the aircraft rotating about
the y axis in positive direction or in negative direction respectively. Positive and negative roll angle is the positive direction or
negative direction rotation angle about the x axis respectively.
However in the ground coordinate system, positive and negative pitch angle is the angle value for the aircraft moving south and
north respectively. Positive and negative roll angle is the angle when the aircraft is moving east and west respectively.
Maximum angle is defined as DJIVirtualStickRollPitchControlMaxAngle;
Minimum angle is defined as DJIVirtualStickRollPitchControlMinAngle;
     </Abstract>
            <Declaration>DJIVirtualStickRollPitchControlModeAngle</Declaration>
            
            <DeclaredIn>DJIFlightController.h</DeclaredIn>
            
            <NodeRef refid="157"/>
        </Token>
        
        <Token>
            <TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/c/econst/DJIVirtualStickRollPitchControlModeVelocity</TokenIdentifier>
            <Abstract type="html">Sets the VirtualStickControlMode roll and pitch values to be a velocity.
In the body coordinate system, positive and negative pitch velocity is for the aircraft moving towards the positive direction or
negative direction along the pitch axis/y axis respectively. Positive and negative roll velocity is when the aircraft is moving towards
the positive direction or negative direction along the roll axis/x axis respectively.
However, in the ground coordinate system, positive and negative pitch velocity is for the aircraft moving east and west respectively.
Positive and negative roll velocity is when the aircraft is moving north and south respectively.
Maximum velocity is defined as DJIVirtualStickRollPitchControlMaxVelocity;
Minimum velocity is defined as DJIVirtualStickRollPitchControlMinVelocity.
     </Abstract>
            <Declaration>DJIVirtualStickRollPitchControlModeVelocity</Declaration>
            
            <DeclaredIn>DJIFlightController.h</DeclaredIn>
            
            <NodeRef refid="157"/>
        </Token>
        
	</File>
</Tokens>